singersroom.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy - Singersroom

GENTLES CREATIVE GROUP, INC (“GCG” or “we” or “us”), is responsible for the content of this Website (as defined in the Terms and Conditions of Use).

Singersroom is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our website. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to information you provide to us offline.

**YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.**

**1\. Personal Information:** When you interact with the Website, you may provide personal information to us (such as your name, email address, date of birth, etc.) or we may collect information when you subscribe to notifications or sign up to receive information from us. We will only collect and use information that is related to our legitimate business interests and in order to better understand your interests and to improve your experience while using this Website.

**2\. Privacy of Minors:** If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please be sure to read this Privacy Policy with your parent and obtain his or her permission before you submit or post any personal information and before you use any features on this Website that require participation or posting your feedback.

**3\. Social Media Plug-Ins:** Social Media plug-ins of social networks such as Facebook, Twitter and Google are integrated on our Website. Where our Website contains a plug-in to a social network, these are clearly marked (e.g. with a Facebook button). If you chose to click on one of these links, your browser connects directly to the servers of the relevant social network. If you are registered on the relevant social network and logged into your account, the social network receives the information that the web page was used by you and may link your personal information to our Website. If you post or share information or content, such as photos, letters, or comments, while participating in online forums on our Website or through your Social Media platform plug-in, depending on your privacy settings this information and your username may become public on the Internet. We cannot prevent further use of this information once it is made public. Also, if you interact with us through a social media platform, plug-in, etc. then you may be permitting us to have on-going access to some limited information from your social network profile (such as name, email address, photo, gender, location and the people and/or sites you follow, etc.). If you do not wish us to have access to your information via your social network, please adjust your privacy settings on the relevant platform or log out of your social network before you visit our Website.

**4\. Cookies:** We use “cookies” or other similar technology (including flash cookies, e-tags, cache browsers, and GIFs, etc.) on the Website. We use cookies to tell us whether you have visited the Website previously or if you are a new visitor and to help us identify Website features in which you have the greatest interest. When you use our Website, we may automatically collect certain personal information that is aggregated with information collected for other users. This information provides us with statistics such as how many users visit the Website and what pages were accessed. We may use anonymous data in the aggregate form for purposes of research or to conduct research-based on viewer demographics, interests and behaviors. Although this data may be based in part on personal information collected from you or your social media platform, it does not identify any users personally. We may share this type of anonymous data with third parties, including our affiliates, agents, service providers, and current and prospective business partners to administer the website and for advertising, promotional and other business purposes.

We may also work with reputable third parties to present advertisements, and engage in data collection, reporting, ad delivery and response time measurement and other analytics using the data collected on our Site and on third-party websites across the Internet and applications over time. These third parties may also use cookies, web beacons or similar technology to perform these activities. They may obtain information about applications you use, websites you visit and other information and browsers in order to serve advertising that may be more relevant to your interests.

**5\. Information for EU Residents**

5.1. Data retention

In the absence of specific retention periods set out in this Privacy Policy, your personal data will be retained only for as long as we need it to fulfill the purpose for which we have collected it and, if applicable, as long as required by legal retention requirements.

5.2. Your Rights

Under the legislation applicable to you, you may be entitled to exercise some or all of the following rights:

  * require (i) access to and/or duplicates of your personal data retained, (ii) receive the personal data concerning you, which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and (iii) to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from our side; where technically feasible you shall have the right to have the personal data transmitted directly from us to another controller;
  * request proper rectification, erasure or restriction of your personal data, e.g. because (i) it is incomplete or inaccurate, (ii) it is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected, or (iii) the consent on which the processing was based has been withdrawn, or (iv) you have taken advantage of an existing right to object to the data processing; in case the personal data is processed by third parties, your request for rectification, erasure or restriction will be forwarded also to such third parties unless this proves impossible or involves disproportionate effort;
  * refuse to provide and – without impact to data processing activities that have taken place before such withdrawal or to any other existing legal justification of the processing activity in question – withdraw your consent to processing of your personal data at any time;
  * object at any time that your personal data will be used for direct marketing purposes, or – based on grounds relating to your particular situation – that your personal data shall be subject to data processing for other purposes;
  * take legal actions in relation to any potential breach of your rights regarding the processing of your personal data, as well as to lodge complaints before the competent data protection regulators; and/or
  * not to be subject to any automated decision making, including profiling (automatic decisions based on data processing by automatic means, for the purpose of assessing several personal aspects) which produce legal effects on you or affects you with similar significance.

You may (i) exercise the rights referred to above or (ii) pose any questions or (iii) make any complaints regarding our data processing by contacting us under the contact details set out below.

You may [**email us**](http://singersroom.com/contact/) if at any time you would like to see the personally identifiable information we hold about you, or to ask us to correct or update this information, or to ask us to delete it. Please contact us if you have questions or wish to take any action with respect to information to which this Privacy Policy applies (see below for contact information).

This Privacy Policy was last updated on Jan 2, 2019. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We do not undertake to provide you with personal notice of any changes. In the event of material changes, we will provide notice by means that are reasonable under the circumstances, such as by posting a notice on the Website. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy means you accept those changes.
